{
    "subject": "resource/The_Cowboy_Way_(album)",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Western_music_(North_America)",
    "human_readable": "The Cowboy Way (album) is a Western music album.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.618442714214325,
            "question": "What genre of music is The Cowboy Way?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6073479056358337,
            "question": "What kind of instruments are typically featured in Western music like The Cowboy Way?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5951991081237793,
            "question": "Can you name some popular songs from The Cowboy Way album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5781549215316772,
            "question": "Are there any famous artists associated with The Cowboy Way album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5778858065605164,
            "question": "What theme does The Cowboy Way album explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5657174587249756,
            "question": "Where could someone listen to The Cowboy Way album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45781347155570984,
            "question": "Are there any historical events or periods that influenced Western music like The Cowboy Way?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20211045444011688,
            "question": "How has Western music evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19430497288703918,
            "question": "What are some other genres of music that share similarities with Western music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18917374312877655,
            "question": "Who might enjoy listening to The Cowboy Way?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Cowboy Way (album) is a Western music album.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4169_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some other genres of music that share similarities with Western music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4169_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Western music evolved over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4169_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical events or periods that influenced Western music like The Cowboy Way?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4169_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4169_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4169_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4169_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4169_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4169_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4169_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4169_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4169_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4169_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4169_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents provided contain information about the album \"The Cowboy Way\", and it is mentioned as a Western music album, with details such as track lists, musicians involved, and awards won by the artists associated with the album."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the album titled \"The Cowboy Way,\" indicating it is part of the Western Music tradition and has won awards in that genre. Therefore, the statement that \"The Cowboy Way (album) is a Western music album\" is supported by the context provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}